Ordu Donald

Lagos 100001 ordudonald8_fh2@indeedemail.com +234 904 905 7097

Experienced graphics designer with a strong background as the Head Graphics Designer at Quadcore Ltd. Possessing over 5 years of professional experience in the field, I have also excelled as a freelance brand identity designer. I bring in-depth knowledge of design principles, along with expertise in utilizing the Adobe Graphics Suite to create visually captivating designs. My skill set extends beyond design, as I prioritize delivering exceptional customer service and understanding the impact of graphics design on businesses.

Personal Details

Currently Employed: No Date of Birth: 1995-11-14

Highest Level of Education: Higher National Diploma

Industry: IT Operations & Helpdesk, Information Design & Documentation, Information Technology,

Media & Communications, Software Development

NYSC Status: Not Applicable

Work Experience

Illustrator

Freelance Marketing-Lagos January 2020 to Present

I create series of illustrations with adobe illustrator.

Brand identity designer

Freelance Marketing-Lagos January 2019 to Present

I provide a design strategy for the brand(startup or pre-existing, big or small),

Then I curate the designs accordingly, branching every brand element to give the brand its proper essence.

Graphics Designer

Freelance Marketing-Lagos January 2019 to Present

Creating/modifying designs for printing.

Senior Graphics Designer

Quadcore Itd.

August 2022 to February 2023

worked remotely as the senior graphics designer and brand identity designer.

Managed the brand's identity and also it's deliverables (prints) and web designs.

Education

Bsc in Computer science (ongoing) in Computer science

ESPAM FORMATION, Benin Republic - Lagos

January 2021 to October 2024

Certificate of Completion in Software engineering

Alx SE program - Lagos August 2023 to September 2024

Senior Secondary

Skills

- Graphics design (5 years)
- Adobe illustrator (5 years)
- Adobe Photoshop (6 years)
- Adobe premiere pro (3 years)
- Frontend development (1 year)
- Video editing (2 years)
- html (2 years)
- reactjs (1 year)

Languages

• English - Fluent

Links

http://be.net/ordudesigns